<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>RimTraits - Medieval Talents</name>
	<author>Sierra</author>
	<packageId>Sierra.RTMT</packageId>
	<url></url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
[h1]Supported Versions:[/h1]
[b]Rimworld 1.2[/b]


[h1]Get [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2244594116]RimTraits - Vanilla Trait Colours[/url] to change your Vanilla Trait Colours to match this mod![/h1]


This mod adds 34 traits defining a pawn's talent, they are mutually exclusive to each other with increasing rarity for the higher tier traits.

This mod operates on the premise that passion doesn’t equal to talent, and talent doesn’t necessarily translate to passion.

You could really love doing something but you could still suck at it. And likewise you can have talent with something but you’re not necessarily passionate about them. These traits also give additional Temperature, Mood, Mental Break and Pain Tolerance buff to compensate for the lack of technology during medieval times, and to represent people's ability to face hardships during less civilized ages.


[b]Note: This mod is meant to be paired up with Medieval and QoL mods made by other authors, using mods that allow for pawn customisation is also highly recommended.[/b]


[b]Balance:[/b]
Balance feedbacks re:balance is appreciated, please do however bear in mind that this mod is balanced around larger colonies (35-80 colonists) that are limited to Medieval-level technologies.


[b]Recommended Mods:[/b]
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1874644848]Character Editor[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1508850027]RimHUD[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1508292711][KV] More Trait Slots - 1.2[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2244594116]RimTraits - Vanilla Trait Colours[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2206957172]RimTraits - General Traits[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1884025115]Oskar Potocki's Vanilla Expanded Collection[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1855885448]Guard For Me[/url]
[/list]


[b]Mod Compatibility:[/b]
[list]
[*][Minor Conflict] May conflict with mods that changes trait colour based on commonality.
[/list]


[url=https://discord.gg/rimworld]Click here to join us on the Community Discord![/url]


[h1]Credits:[/h1]
[list]
[*]Taranchuk for his C# wizardry.
[/list]


[h1]Recent Changes:[/h1]
[b]Update 15: Normal Update[/b]
[list]
[*]Nerfed damage reduction for Hero from 75% to 60%.
[*]Nerfed damage reduction for Adventurer from 45% to 35%.
[/list]

[b]Update 16: Major Update[/b]
[list]
[*]Change: This mod no longer require De-generalize Work as a mod pre-requisite.
[*]Change: RimWorld 1.0 is no longer supported.
[*]Fix: All pawns should now be guaranteed to spawn with 1 talent.
[*]Buff: All pawns now have a reduced Food/Rest/Recreation need decay.
[/list]
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
